http://www.bodmanlongley.com/terms-of-use/

Ann Arbor201 S. Division StreetSuite 400Ann Arbor, MI 48104T 734-761-3780Cheboygan229 Court StreetP.O. Box 405Cheboygan, MI 49721T 231-627-8000Detroit1901 St. Antoine Street6th Floor at Ford FieldDetroit, MI 48226T 313-259-7777Grand Rapids99 Monroe Avenue NWSuite 300Grand Rapids, MI 49503T 616-205-4330Troy201 W. Big Beaver RoadSuite 500Troy, MI 48084T 248-743-6000Go to page >
ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ
view all
office
Ann Arbor OfficeCheboygan OfficeDetroit OfficeGrand Rapids OfficeTroy Office
language
ArabicFrenchItalianNorwegianPolishPortugueseRussianSpanish
professional affiliations
American Academy of Hospital AttorneysAmerican Arbitration Association (AAA)®American Bankruptcy InstituteAmerican Bar AssociationAmerican College of Mortgage AttorneysAmerican Health Lawyers AssociationAmerican Inns of Court (AIC)Ann Arbor Area Community Foundation Network of Professional AdvisorsAssociation for Corporate Growth (ACG)Attorneys' Liability Assurance Society (ALAS) Ltd.Catholic Lawyers Society of DetroitCheboygan County Bar AssociationDefense Research InstituteDetroit Bar Association (DBA)Detroit Economic ClubDetroit Society for Human Resource ManagementDetroit Treasury Management AssociationEconomic Club of Grand RapidsFINRA®Federal Bar AssociationFederalist SocietyFinancial and Estate Planning Council of Metropolitan DetroitGrand Rapids Bar AssociationGrand Rapids Women's IP Forum (GRIP)Great Lakes Area TE/GE CouncilGreat Lakes Environmental Law CenterIllinois State Bar Association (ISBA)Indiana State Bar AssociationInstitute for Continuing Legal EducationInternational Bar AssociationInternational Franchise AssociationInternational Trademark Association (INTA)Leadership DetroitMacomb County Bar AssociationMacomb County Chamber of CommerceMichigan Association of Certified Public AccountantsMichigan Committee on Model Civil Jury InstructionsMichigan Townships AssociationMichigan Venture Capital AssociationMichigan Women in Finance Michigan Women's Tax AssociationNational Association of State Bar Tax SectionsNational Business Aviation AssociationNational Catholic Education AssociationNational Diocesan Attorneys AssociationOakland County Bar Association (OCBA)Oakland County Bar FoundationProfessional Responsibility CounselorsSmall Business Association of MichiganSociety for Human Resource ManagementState Bar of CaliforniaState Bar of FloridaState Bar of IllinoisState Bar of MichiganState Bar of Michigan FoundationState Bar of NevadaState Bar of TexasState Bar of WisconsinThe Chicago Bar AssociationTurnaround Management Association® University of Michigan Law School - Alumni-Student Mentoring ProgramWashtenaw Community CollegeWashtenaw County American Red CrossWashtenaw County Bar AssociationWashtenaw County Circuit CourtWashtenaw Estate Planning CouncilWayne County Mediation TribunalWolverine Bar AssociationWomen Lawyers Association of MichiganWomen Lawyers Association of Michigan Foundation
practice/industry
Appellate LawAutomotive and IndustrialAviation Law and FinanceBankingBankruptcy and Debtor-Creditor RightsBusinessCOVID-19 Response TeamConstructionData Privacy and SecurityEmerging Companies and Venture CapitalEmployee Benefits and Executive CompensationEnterprise ProcurementEnvironmental LawExempt Organizations and Impact InvestingHealth CareHigh Net WorthInsuranceIntellectual PropertyLitigation and Alternative Dispute ResolutionMunicipal Law and FinanceReal EstateTaxWorkplace Law
position
AssociateIn MemoriamMemberOf CounselPro Bono CounselSenior AssociateSenior AttorneyStaff Attorney
school
Albion CollegeAlma CollegeAmerican University, TheAquinas CollegeBaylor UniversityBowling Green State UniversityBrooklyn Law SchoolCase Western Reserve UniversityCentral Michigan UniversityChicago-Kent College of Law — Illinois Institute of TechnologyCleveland-Marshall College of Law — Cleveland State UniversityDePaul University College of LawEastern Michigan UniversityEmory UniversityFlorida A&M UniversityFlorida State UniversityGeorge Washington University Law School, TheHarvard Law SchoolIndiana University Maurer School of Law — BloomingtonKalamazoo CollegeLouisiana State UniversityLouisiana State University Law CenterLoyola University Chicago School of LawMarquette UniversityMiami UniversityMichigan State UniversityMichigan State University College of LawMitchell Hamline School of LawNew York University Law SchoolNortheastern University School of LawNorthwestern University Pritzker School of LawOakland UniversityOhio State University Moritz College of Law, TheSacred Heart Seminary CollegeSoutheast Missouri State UniversitySouthern Methodist UniversityUniversity of ChicagoUniversity of Detroit MercyUniversity of Detroit Mercy School of LawUniversity of FloridaUniversity of IllinoisUniversity of Illinois College of LawUniversity of KansasUniversity of MichiganUniversity of Michigan - DearbornUniversity of Michigan Law SchoolUniversity of MinnesotaUniversity of Minnesota Law SchoolUniversity of Nevada-Las Vegas William S. Boyd School of LawUniversity of Notre Dame Law SchoolUniversity of PennsylvaniaUniversity of RichmondUniversity of RochesterUniversity of Southern CaliforniaUniversity of St. ThomasUniversity of Toledo College of Law, TheUniversity of WindsorUniversity of WisconsinUniversity of Wisconsin Law SchoolVanderbilt UniversityWabash CollegeWake Forest University Law SchoolWashington University School of LawWashington University in St. Louis School of LawWayne State UniversityWayne State University Law SchoolWayne State University Medical SchoolWellesley CollegeWestern Michigan UniversityWestern Michigan University Cooley Law School
bar admissions
CaliforniaDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaIllinoisMichiganMinnesotaNevadaNew YorkOhioPennsylvaniaProvince of OntarioTexas
Go to page >
Privacy Policy
Please Read Carefully
Effective September 1, 2016
Bodman PLC (Bodman) is committed to the privacy and security of data in our possession. The Privacy Policy (this Policy) applies to your use of www.bodmanlaw.com (this Site) and any services or correspondence occurring or originating on the Site. This Policy describes how this Site uses the personal information you provide to this Site.
Attorney-Client Relationship and Privilege. This Policy does not apply to information provided to us in the course of our attorney-client relationships or protected by confidentiality, the attorney-client privilege, the attorney work product doctrine or any other applicable protection. This Policy does not create an attorney-client relationship with visitors to this Site and does not detract from any of the protections resulting from any existing attorney-client relationship.
Agreement. By Using this Site, you agree to this Policy and should read this Policy carefully.
Information Collected and Information is Used. You may visit this Site without providing personal information about yourself. However, this Site does collect certain information about your computer and activities, including (without limitation) information about your operating system, browser software, Internet Protocol (IP) address and the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through and from our website, including date and time. Bodman may use this information to improve the performance of or administer this Site. This Site also uses “cookies”. Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information that can be downloaded to your device when you visit a website. The cookies we use help to provide you with a better experience while on this Site. Although you can disable cookies on your device by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser, doing so may limit your ability to view our Site. Bodman may disclose any information deemed necessary (in Bodman’s sole discretion) to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request.
Information You Submit to Bodman Through this Site. If you join one or more of our mailing lists or otherwise submit personal information to us through this Site, Bodman will use that information for the purpose for which it was collected and for other reasonably related purposes Bodman determines are appropriate. Bodman may provide your information to third parties for the processing of information solely for Bodman’s benefit. We will not provide your information to any third party for marketing purposes except in connection with information requests you make that involve third parties or in connection with events that involve presentations or sponsorship by third parties.
Links. Links to web sites that are not operated by or for Bodman (Third Party Sites) are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave this Site, be providing information to a Third Party Site or both. This Privacy Policy does not apply to Third Party Sites, including the links to those Third Party Sites. Bodman has not reviewed and does not have control over Third Party Sites or the information collected by and policies (or lack of policies) on Third Party Sites. Bodman’s placement of a link to or material from Third Party Sites is do not endorse or make any representations about Third Party Sites or any information, software or other products, services or materials found on Third Party Sites. If you decide to access any of the Third Party Sites listed on this Site, you do so at your own risk.
Transfer of Information Across National Borders. This Site is operated on servers within the United States. Where permitted by law and if required by applicable law, such as the European Economic Area or European Union, you expressly consent to the transfer of your personal information to, and the collection and processing of personal information in the United States. In giving this consent, you acknowledge your understanding that the laws on holding, processing, using and transferring personal information in the United States may vary and be less protective of your privacy than laws of your state or country.
Children’s Privacy. We are committed to complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Our Site and services are not directed to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we receive personal information that we discover was provided by a child under the age of 13, we will promptly destroy such information. Schools and parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider the use of other means to provide a child-friendly, online environment.
Security. This Site is not designed to store sensitive personal information such as financial, health or educational records and you should not use this Site to provide sensitive personal information. Bodman believes this Site uses commercially reasonable measures to secure the personal information you may provide. However, we cannot and do not assure these measures will be sufficient to protect against all efforts to gain unauthorized access to information.
Amendment. Bodman may amend this Policy at its discretion. If Bodman amends this Policy, Bodman will provide notice by appropriate means. Except when required by law, this Policy may be amended prior to any notice of an amendment is provided to you. Any information collected under a previous version of this Policy will be subject to the terms of the new Policy.
Contacts. If you would like to request access to the personal data you have provided on this Site or if you have any queries, claims, or the like, send an e-mail to Cathy Borza, Director of Administration, cborza@bodmanlaw.com
Data Controller. The data controller for this website is: Anthony J. Allegrina, Communications Manager, aallegrina@bodmanlaw.com.
